♪ In the not too distant
future, way down ♪
♪ in Deep 13. ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank
were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp by the name
of Mike, just a regular Joe ♪
♪ they didn't like. ♪
♪ Their experiment needed
a good test case, ♪
♪ so they conked him on the ♪
♪ noggin and they
shot him into space ♪
♪ Let me go ♪
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies, ♪
♪ The worst we can find. ♪
♪ La-la-la. ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all, ♪
♪ and we'll monitor his mind. ♪
♪ La-la-la. ♪
♪ Now, keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ where the movies
begin or end. ♪
♪ La-la-la. ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
with the help of his robot ♪
♪ friends. ♪
- Robot roll call.
Cambot.
- Show yourself.
- Gypsy.
- I'm not ready.
- Tom Servo.
- Hello, there.
- Crow.
- That's one O.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts. ♪
♪ La-la-la. ♪
♪ Repeat to yourself
it's just a show, ♪
♪ I should really just relax. ♪
♪ For "Mystery Science
Theater 3000." ♪
(humming Christmas song)
- Season's greetings, everyone.
Welcome to the
Satellite of Love.
- Yay!
- You know, you're just in
time for our caroling session.
We've got a nice,
hot mug of cocoa.
As you can see,
we're all bundled up
and we're ready to go.
- So just sit back, relax...
- And listen to Tom
drown out the rest of us.
- Hey.
- Come on, you guys,
it's Christmas.
That's OK.
- Yeah, come on.
- OK, everyone ready?
Get your places.
Here's your note.
- Ok.
(Music playing)
- (singing) Rum,
pum-pum-pum, pum, pum.
- (singing) Rum.
Pum.
Rum pum pum.
Rum.
(Shrieking)
- [Computer] We'll
be right back.
I think.
Noel.
(Theme music)
(Whimpering)
- Gee, Mike, why don't we
make it a holiday tradition
that you smash my
head and give Crow
extensive third-degree
burns, huh?
- What can I say?
I'm sorry.
- Oh, don't sweat it, Mike.
Ah, with any luck the burns
will have healed by Labor Day.
- Oh, look.
Yukon Cornelius and
Herbie are calling.
- So cool.
- Ooh!
This is going to be so great.
(Shivering)
- Oh, brass monkeys, Frank.
Ugh, brass monkeys.
- Merry Christmas, Dr. F.
- Uh, merry what?
Oh, what's that?
Oh.
- Open it.
- Oh, Frank.
- I shaved my head and
got you a watch fob.
- Oh, you... argh!
You... oh, you sold
your hair and got
me this beautiful watch fob.
Oh, thank you.
- Sold my hair?
No.
- Oh.
Well, it's very beautiful.
Thank you.
Well, it's very nice.
Watch fob.
I'll be right back.
What are you doing, Clay?
- [Forrester] I'm just
getting your gift, Frank.
- Oh, you didn't
have to do that.
- Oh.
No, I... I wanted to.
It's a... a $25 savings bond.
- It's made out to you.
- Oh.
Uh, here.
I'll just, uh, sign
it over to you.
There you go.
There.
Well, it matures in 2023.
You'll want to keep
that in a safe place.
- So I guess it'll be
worth a lot of money
in about 30 years or so, huh?
- Well, $25.
What's your deal, Nelson?
- Well, Crow, I... I drew
your name, so here it is.
- Whoa.
Ooh, wow.
Oh, wow.
A Steve Alaimo album.
Ooh, wow.
Oh, how did you know I needed...
- This is a good one too.
This has the extended
mix of "Don't
Let the Sun Catch You Crying."
- Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Ooh.
Oh, Servo, open mine.
- Ok.
Mike, would you mind?
- Oh, right.
- Oh.
- No.
No.
No way.
The 1991 drug ID handbook?
This is too good.
Oh, look.
Electrolyte component chart.
The full pharmacokinetics.
I love it.
Thank you, Crow.
- Oh, you're welcome.
- Open mine, Mike.
Open mine.
- Oh, the big one, OK.
OK, here it is.
Oh, wow.
Great sweater, Gyps.
Thanks.
Look at that.
It says, uh, Joike on it.
- Yeah, well, I... I started
knitting it for the other guy
a long time ago.
And... and then,
well... well, you know.
(Laughter)
- I love it.
Hey, don't you have
something for Gypsy?
- Oh yeah, it's right down
there. Would you get it for me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's some of
them, uh, underwear
in a candy cane, kind of cute.
Thought you might like it, Gyps.
- Oh.
Oh, no.
Oh, don't start.
Oh, No.
What?
It's...
(giggling)
- These guys.
- 30 years, $25.
And I shaved my head for you?
- Well, you didn't
have to, baldy.
- My hair!
My beautiful head
of TV's Frank hair.
(sobbing)
- Your movie today, Mark,
is called "Santa Claus."
It's a thoughtful,
well-shot documentary
about the Crimean War.
- It's a stupid
Mexican kids' movie.
(sobbing)
- Oh, and Servo, I
got you a dreidel.
- Cool.
(Buzzer sounding)
- Oh, movie sign!
- Movie sign!
- My dreidel!
(Christmas music)
- Oh, Murray, the
ceiling needs painting.
(humming Christmas song)
- I saw Mommy killing
Santa Claus underneath
the mistletoe last murder.
- Joe Don Baker is Santa Claus.
- Hey, wait, this is
a fascist Santa Claus.
- Yeah, at the end of the movie,
Santa gets hung upside down.
- Well, at least he made the
sleigh rides run on time.
- "Santa Claus versus
the Aztec Mummy."
- El Santa.
El Santa will save us.
(humming Christmas song)
- Ole!
- Think it's really a good
idea to jingle all the way?
- Hmm.
Hmm.
- It's a free-trade Christmas.
(Christmas music)
- Music's mocking us.
- Hey, all right,
Christmas is going
to Mexico for spring break.
- Ooh, dude.
- Partay!
- (singing) Jingle bells, Batman
smells, Robin laid an egg.
Batmobile lost a wheel
and the Joker got away.
- Oh, that's such
cute wrapping paper.
Yeah, Doris got it at Newbury's.
- Save it.
Oh, I mean save it.
Save the wrapping paper.
(Christmas music)
- Well, apparently
they are committed
to jingling all the way.
- Did Danny Elfman
write this music?
Elfman?
- Yeah.
- Danny Elfman?
- I heard this film was
taken away from Ken Smith
and re-edited by Santa himself.
- Away up in the heavens,
far out in space,
in a beautiful gold and
crystal palace right
above the North Pole, lives a
kind and jolly old gentleman.
- My dad.
- Santa Claus, also
known as St. Nicholas.
- No distinguishing
marks or scars.
- The best friend of boys
and girls everywhere.
But let's move in
for a closer look.
Come along.
- St. Barbie the Archangel.
- Stay.
Stay.
(Santa laughing)
- Action Jesus.
Manger sold separately.
(Jolly laughter continues)
(Sinister laugh from mike)
- I will rule the world.
(Sinister laughter)
- I think Santa would be in his
sweats on his days off, huh?
- Ha, it's almost Christmas,
and I must finish the toys
for all the good
children on Earth.
I hope you'll pardon me, but
you know I mustn't be late.
- Just humor him.
(humming Christmas song)
- Why does he have that Air
Force star above his door?
- Well, Santa flew 23
missions over North Korea.
- You don't say.
- Now Santa Claus
on "Pipe Dreams."
- It's Liberace Santa.
- Now Santa plays "The
Six Wives of Henry VIII.'
(humming Christmas song)
- Now he doesn't know
the words to this song?
You'd think that
he'd know the words.
- This is Santa's
Toy Land, a sort
of international toy factory.
Here are gathered boys and
girls of different
races and creeds.
They have come from
many lands to help
Santa bring joy and happiness
to all of the Earth's children.
These little helpers
are from Africa.
(Drumming)
- Oh, brother.
- Oh, no.
Boo!
- That's good.
- Ted Danson's comedy school.
- (singing) Ho, ho, ho, ho,
stayin' alive, stayin' alive.
- I think David Byrne
stole this music.
(Drumming)
- Here are Santa's
helpers from Spain.
(Singing in spanish)
- Hey, children on the verge
of a nervous breakdown.
(Singing in spanish)
- Clap on.
Clap off.
(Singing in spanish)
- Whee!
- (singing) I love him.
I love him.
And where he goes I'll follow.
- Tots from China
lend a hand as well.
(Singing in Chinese)
- Bertolucci is brought
in to direct this scene.
(Singing in Chinese)
- Pick it up, kids,
I'm feeling frisky.
(Singing in Chinese)
- (singing) We are
forced to sing.
(Singing in Chinese)
- Hey, could we move on to
a country with some rhythm?
- One more time!
(Shrill singing)
- Ugh.
- Sorry about that, folks.
- Boys and girls from England
- Have rotten teeth.
- Crow.
- What?
- (singing) London Bridge is
falling down, falling down,
falling down.
- Feel it.
Get down with your
bad Santa self.
Whoo!
(Singing in Japanese)
- Japan also helps Santa.
- By investing in his
toy-making corporation,
they now own Santa
lock, stock, and barrel.
- OK, back to cram school.
- Santa has a rich
fantasy life, I think
- Some weird elves
you see there.
- You know, if seasonal holiday
depression has a soundtrack,
this is it.
- Yeah.
Yep.
(Singing in Japanese)
- Ooh.
Wow.
(Singing stops)
- Thank you.
- Talented children
from the Orient.
- Are not here today.
(Music playing)
- Uh.
Now you're... uh, you're dancing
on my keyboard, (mumbling).
(Music playing)
- Get it on in the morning, now.
Uh!
Ha!
(Music playing)
- Even Russia has a delegation.
- Currently under
surveillance by the CIA.
(Upbeat Russian music playing)
- Ho. Ho.
Ho.
Ho. Ho.
Hey!
(Music playing)
- Santa makes them sing 16
hours a day for $2 an hour.
- The group from France
stinks to high heaven.
- Servo.
- Sorry, but well,
that's a known fact.
- It is not.
- Yvette and Pierre.
- [Child] You stupid Americans.
(Singing in french)
- Ooh, vive la France.
- [Person] Retreat!
Retreat!
- Servo, what is it
with you and the French?
- German boys and
girls help Santa too.
- [Person] Klink, you
are a terrible singer.
- You're absolutely right.
I am a terrible singer.
- How would you like to
sing at the Russian front?
- Well, my father
was a very famous...
- Shut up, please.
- Yes, sir.
- Better be careful
with these guys.
They could invade
the North Pole.
Germans, you see.
(Singing in German)
- I just want to know one thing.
When are Donny and Marie
coming through the door?
- Never.
- Me too.
- Don't say anything
to upset them.
- Germans.
The Von Trapp Family
Singers here, huh?
(Music playing)
- Here is a happy
song from Italy.
(Singing in Italian)
- So some Italians,
hot and spicy.
(Singing in Italian)
- So is this neo-realism?
- [Person] OK, we're
gonna wax Santa.
He's trying to muscle in
on the Easter Bunny's turf.
- Ok.
OK, great, you've
offended everyone now.
- The islands of the Caribbean.
- Have nothing to
do with this movie.
(Singing in spanish)
- [Person] Legalize it, mon.
- (singing) Get up, stand up.
Stand up for your rights.
- [Person] Ho, ho, irie, man.
Irie.
Something special
in that stocking.
(Singing in spanish)
- Hey, it's a young Sheila E.
- Next up in the junior
vocalist category, Thailand.
Ha.
- Bring it on ho-ho-home, kids.
- The South American group
includes Brazil and Argentina.
- And a few other countries
not worth mentioning right now.
(Music playing)
- Ho, Santa's doing
the forbidden dance.
- Huh!
Oh! Good God.
Oh.
Waka-chicka,
waka-chicka, waka-chicka.
Huh. Get down.
Huh.
Get some soul.
- Hey, Mike, has she been read
her Carmen Miranda rights?
- Doh!
- Oh.
- Eh.
Huh.
- The countries of
Central America.
- Are a threat to Santa's
vital security interests.
- Hey, hey, they're the same
kids from the other countries.
They'll be playing
the Egyptians next.
(Singing in spanish)
- (singing) The house
began to twitch.
(Singing in spanish)
- Hooray!
USA, whoo!
- USA, whoo!
- Children from the USA.
- Are too spoiled and
lazy to help Santa.
Ha, ha.
There, that makes it better.
- (singing) Little lamb.
Little lamb.
- Ugh.
Cop killer.
C... c... cop killer.
- Uh, excuse me.
You're rhythm guitar.
I'm lead.
- (singing) It followed
her to school...
- This is the
really new country.
- He has a generous helping
of ears, doesn't he?
- Young Jeff Healey.
- (singing) Which was
against the rules.
- A neighborly group
of helpers from Mexico.
- Are over-accessorized.
(Singing in spanish)
- Whoa, they found a
little demon puppy.
They found Chucky.
- Relax.
Relax, it's just Keith Magnuson.
- Oh, that's worse.
- Oh, you're right.
(Singing in Spanish)
- It's Los Lobos' first gig.
- Oh.
- Kid, that's not
how you play a rifle.
(Singing in spanish)
- Whoo!
(Theme music)
(Chuckling)
- Hello, there.
- Santa, do you like this devil?
- Why, he owns my soul.
- Devil?
Now, let's see.
Don't think anybody
ordered this.
- It's not a popular item.
- Well, now, how does it work.
What is the sense of it?
- Like this, Santa.
You must light it.
- Let's have it.
- No, my eyes!
My eyes!
My beard's on fire.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
- Jamie Farr.
- I'm positively evil.
- Devil's got a really
weird scene going down here.
- You're gonna burn, burn,
burn those calories off.
- Well, he may be the
Devil, but he sure
knows how to fill his day.
- Oh, they've got those nice
fur-lined slippers, all of them
there.
- Mmm.
- Coven.
- Oh, I suppose Hell
got an NEA grant.
- You'd figure after an eternity
of this, they'd be better.
- Maybe they're over-practiced.
- Try it again.
- I, Lucifer, King
of Hades, command
you to stop and disappear.
- I'm trying to sleep here.
- Begone, all of you.
- Uh, is it hot in here?
Hot?
Uh-huh.
- You, Pitch, chief of all my
demons, must listen closely.
The time is almost here when
you must abandon
the brimstone pits
and journey up to Earth.
- Yes.
Earth, yes.
- But this time
you must not fail,
as you've done in the past.
- No, not in the past.
- You must not be defeated by
that bearded old goat, Santa
Claus.
If you do not succeed in making
all the children of the Earth
do evil, you shall be punished.
And instead of
red-hot coals, you
would eat chocolate ice cream.
- No.
No, Lucifer, king of
all the evil spirits.
- Clark Gable in Hell.
- By the horns of everything
satanic I beg you.
To live, I must have heat.
Frozen meals are bad for
me, especially chocolate.
It's very bad for my digestion,
which is so delicate.
- And I'm lactose intolerant.
- Yes, I promise, oh
priceless prince of Hades,
that by many words I will
finish off Santa forever, induce
children to commit
terrible deeds,
and make Santa Claus angry.
- Go out, then, and show the
world who is its real master.
- So be it, Lucifer.
- You know, that Lucifer
is like Satan... from Hell.
- Wow.
- Demons of Hades,
transport me to Earth.
(Laughter)
- And so the Devil
rose to Earth.
You heard what he
said to Lucifer.
But will he be able
to keep his promise?
- Yeah, it wasn't as
funny as I thought.
(humming Christmas song)
- Ho, ho, ho.
- Whoa.
Now, this is good
old-fashioned nightmare fuel.
(Laughter)
- Hey, look, the
ghost of Ross Perot.
- Santa's army of
walking corpses.
- On Earth, the children can
hardly wait for Christmas Day.
They gaze longingly
at the toys they
hope Santa will bring them.
Here is a good little boy
whose daddy is quite rich.
- He's a lobbyist for
the insurance industry.
- Yeah, let's get out of here.
I'm quite rich, you know,
lots of things to do.
Rich.
(Christmas music)
- This mother, on the
other hand, is very poor.
- Aw.
- And this is her
daughter Lupita,
whose fondest dream is to
own a doll... any doll.
- He is aggressively cute.
(Santa laughing)
- Santa's laughter
mocks the poor.
- I'll have to get past
the security system.
(Santa laughing)
- Heh.
Well, anyway.
- Uh, question, Mr. Santa.
Uh.
- All right, come along.
I gotta buy a bra.
(Christmas music)
- Who are these three?
Say, it's rude to push
and shove like that.
- Ma Barker's killer brood.
- The Devil likes
rude little boys,
and it doesn't take
him long to find them.
They're just right
for his evil plan.
- Just act natural.
- Hey, buddy, could
you lose the horns?
I'm trying to see.
- Devil's really chewing
up the scenery here, huh?
- Well, one thing is certain.
The Devil has turned
them against Santa Claus.
- Oh, Officer Krupke,
da, da, da, da.
- Suddenly he's with them again.
- You can't be in
our club, Satan.
- Out of nowhere, he
produces three rocks,
and his evil plan
goes into action.
- Oh, boy.
- Uh-oh.
- This is bad.
- And that ain't good.
- Ho, ho.
Ow!
- And Satan scores.
- Darn that Devil.
Oh, I'm sorry,
but that old Devil
is always annoying
me with his mischief.
- If I could only go down there
now, I'd put him in his place.
- Oh, big talker.
- But everyone knows
I can only go down
to Earth on Christmas
Eve, and not before.
- In the meantime...
(speaking foreign language)
(Speaking foreign language)
- Huh?
- A short while ago, I
saw the Devil whispering
to four children, and one
was a poor little girl.
- Narc.
- Do you know who they are?
- I've got their names.
The bad boys are...
- No, no, no, no.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
- The naughty boys
are not important.
They will get punished
in due course.
The ones I must reward
are the other children,
like the good little girl.
- I've got their
names right here.
The girl is called...
- Uh, better look through
the telescope, Pedro.
- What?
- We'll find out
what they're doing.
- There's a sliver?
- This is Santa's
magic observatory.
What wonderful instruments.
The year scope.
The tele talker that
knows everything.
The cosmic telescope.
The master eye.
- The pleasure mouth.
- Nothing that happens on Earth
is unknown to Santa Claus.
- Thanks to Liz Smith.
- By thy magic powers,
look for the child
we're seeking, whether
she is in a cave
or behind a million mountains.
- Wow, Santa's got
the dirt on everybody.
- That is a mouth, isn't it?
- All ready.
- Whoa.
- Santa's tendrils
reach far and wide.
There is no hiding from
the Claus organization.
- Huh? What?
Huh?
Oh, Sandy Duncan.
Ha.
- Kid's positioning
himself to replace Santa.
- Uh, yeah.
- This weird enough
for you, folks?
How does this make
you feel about Santa?
- I think I found the girl?
- Where?
- A dame?
Spread out, kid.
- In Mexico.
- Phew.
Oh yeah, he really
zeroed in on her.
(Organ music playing)
- Oh.
- (singing) Incense
and peppermints...
- "Puppet Master 3."
- Yes, it's Lupita, all right.
- Huh.
- And she's still Dreaming
about that doll she wants.
- Oh, it looks like
the puppet version
of "My Dinner With Andre."
- Satan's been busy, I see.
(Music playing)
- Good evening, Buffalo.
We are Santa Klaws, and we
have just one question for you.
Are you ready to be merry?
- Yes.
- I said, are you
ready to be merry?
- Yes!
- Then stuff this
in your stocking.
One, two, three, four.
- (singing) I have
slain the Grinch.
I have broken his spell.
I am the warrior of Christmas,
the world we will tell.
- Christmas time.
Free your mind.
Let love unwind.
- (singing) The warrior of
Christmas has cast out the neon
prince.
Hail the new Claus.
Your hair he will rinse.
(Cheering)
(Music playing)
- (singing) Silver bells
fall from your nose.
Santa Claus and mistletoe.
Rudolph's found the
emperor's clothes.
- (singing) Blitzen,
let's explore.
Joy to the world.
Oh!
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Buffalo.
We love you.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
We love you.
(Theme music)
- We're Saddam and The Fitz.
- Huh?
- Oh, no.
This is wrong somehow.
(Sigh)
- We can only hope that the
stars don't go too deep.
Come on, I gotta
go look for a slip.
- And now the hollow feeling
that follows any puppet show.
- Huh?
- Lupita isn't thinking of
stealing that doll, is she.
- Society owes me.
- No, Lupita.
You shouldn't steal.
Put it back.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm the narrator.
I shouldn't get so involved.
- Huh?
- Lupita.
Lupita, come here.
- Run, Lupita, run.
- Do I need accessories too?
I'm at a moral crossroads, Mom.
Aw.
- It's yours.
Nobody saw you take it, Lupita.
They have more, and
they won't miss it.
What does one
little doll matter?
Don't you see?
You haven't got any toys.
- He makes a
convincing argument.
- Don't listen to him, Lupita.
It's bad to steal.
And you'll be sorry.
- Ah, the classic battle
between evil and the narrator.
- That's right, put it back.
- I guess that's better.
- Good girl.
(Muttering in frustration)
- Ow.
Don't you ever do that again.
- Way to defeat Satan, honey.
- How are you
gonna fence a doll?
- Oh, jeez.
- Hey, silly girl.
Now you'll have to
do without a dolly.
Little girls must do or do
without the things they like.
Now!
- That's not true, Lupita.
If you're good, somehow
you'll be rewarded.
- Well, that's not strictly
true either, but...
- Help me.
- Hmm.
- Cable pays off
in so many ways.
Ha.
- Hooray for her.
Hooray for her.
All my friends can
ignore the Devil.
All they need to win is
to be good in spirit.
- And the other children?
- Come, Pedro, find them.
- Round up the usual suspects.
- Santa's top executive, Pedro.
- By thy magic powers,
look for the child
we're seeking, whether
he is in a cave
or behind a million mountains.
Ok.
- Now, Pedro, did I tell
you to summon demons?
- We got dolls.
- It's the "Trilogy
of Terror" dolls.
- So where's Mrs. Claus?
- Oh, she winters in Lauderdale.
- Oh.
(high pitched sounds)
- Ow.
- Do I have tinnitus, or
does anyone else hear that?
- What?
- Increasingly paranoid,
Santa's obsession with security
begins to hinder
everyday operations.
- Uh, shouldn't Santa
have a bench warrant
to install these things?
- Mmm, sugar plums.
Dancing.
Ah.
- He's sleeping soundly.
His dream will appear
on the dream scope.
- Hey, that's wrong.
- Connect the antenna
for the dream scope.
- Magic kiss carpets.
- Hey, a Van Gogh fan.
- Ow.
- Well, Pedro, what's on
the dessert tray, huh?
- Pop-O-Matic pops the dice.
- It's the ultimate bubble.
(Coughing)
- No, not that dream.
No.
- Let's watch the
little rich boy's dream.
- And the corruption
inherent in his life.
- How strange.
And what large gift boxes.
Would these be toys?
Why, they contain what
a child loves best.
- A maitre d'.
- His parents.
- It's your new mom.
- Ah.
- Hey, this is a dream,
a two-parent house.
- I see.
- We need to go and
leave you again.
The baby sitter is in the
box over in the corner.
- I miss my mom.
(Speaking foreign language)
- A dream is a wish
that the heart makes.
- Or something like that.
- Then this child is not worthy.
He gets everything he wishes
just by asking his parents.
- The only thing
this child wants...
- Is fear itself.
is the love of his parents.
- Don't they love him?
- Maybe they do.
And maybe they don't.
- Oh, jeez, he's waffling.
- But soon we will
find out the truth.
- And Lupita?
What do you think
she might wish?
- If she's already sleeping, we
might be able to see her dream.
- Kids, this is so Jungian.
- Santa.
Uh, Santa, yo.
- Hey Kringle, snap out of it!
Jeez.
Whoa.
(Coughing)
- Huh?
Honey, Santa's looking
in on our daughter again.
- Honey, does this
crowbar look OK here?
- Well, they're not too poor to
afford an insurance calendar,
I see.
- It was nice of Marcel Duchamp
to let them use his apartment.
- I wonder if our
child is dreaming.
- Well, actually we enter
several dream stages
during a typical night.
There's REM.
Then there's the... oh, sorry.
- Let's go bowling.
- I recall when I
was a little girl.
- Oh god, here we go.
- I often would dream
of great riches.
- The old "I could have
been a dancer" story.
- But I have all the things
I wish for and not a care
in the world.
- That was before the abysmal
mess called my marriage.
Sorry.
- Confounded Devil.
Why can't he leave Lupita alone?
- Hey, he's just doing his job.
- Whoa, his breath smells
like Underwood Deviled Ham.
(Snoring)
(Panting)
- I think he got those horns
in Jackson Hole, Wyoming.
- Maybe his breath
is fresh and minty.
- Ooh.
- That's disgusting.
- Just look at
that old busybody.
He'll make Lupita
want to steal again.
He'll be part of her dream.
- [Girl] Uh, Santa, could you
notch the volume down a little?
We're right here.
- Better look at her dream now.
- Better get on the horn with
God since Satan's involved now.
- Pick your
refrigerator, Lupita.
- (singing) I can get a
dolly, and the top is blue.
She is very pretty
and her name is Sue.
- Everybody sing along.
- (singing) When I took her
shopping, she got sick...
- Must admit, she's got
a way with a ballad.
- (singing) When I took
her home, she got well...
- Take it home, Lupita.
(Theme music)
- Why don't you steal us?
We can all be yours.
- No.
You know that stealing is bad.
And I want to be good.
- But you must learn to steal.
- I'm Martha Raye.
- No.
You know stealing is bad.
And I want to be good.
- We dolls don't like
good little girls.
- No.
To steal is evil, and I
don't want to be evil.
- Perhaps I could...
- You want to be evil.
You want the doll.
- No.
You know stealing is evil,
and I don't want to be evil.
- I think David Hume had...
- Steal us, and we
will all be yours.
- Well, it's a moralistic...
- I don't want to be evil.
And telling lies is evil.
- You wan to be good, Eh?
Don't want to be bad?
- No.
- The kid should be a lawyer.
- Stealing is bad.
And I want to be good.
- Well, then, you'll
never have a doll.
(Cackling)
- What the heck was that?
- Mama.
Mama.
- I had the 'Nam dream.
(Coughing)
- Yeah, let's try
to avoid that dream.
- Believe me, that old Pitch
is going to pay for this.
- Old what?
- The very minute
I get to Earth, he
will pay for what he is doing.
- And the three little boys,
the ones who broke the window,
maybe they have
done more mischief.
- Yeah, thanks, Tex.
(Speaking foreign language)
- Yes, look for them.
- Get them now.
I want to see them fry.
(Speaking foreign language)
- That big thing Gamera
is taking over the city.
(Speaking foreign language)
It figures Santa would
be a ham operator.
- Oh, it all makes sense now.
- Oh.
- Well, Santa should have
hired some taller kids.
- Oh, lost my contact.
- Clown-o-meter on overload.
(Electronic noises)
- The three boys are
beneath a large bed,
but they are speaking
in a low voice.
- They are looking
at "Playboys."
- Now we will learn exactly
what they are planning.
- Huh?
The J. Paul Getty Jr. scope.
- No.
- Oh.
- It's an oscillating
fan with an ear attached.
Period.
- Ok.
- Hmm.
Huh.
- Or not.
- I've got it.
- Mick Jagger.
- We'll break our
neighbor's window.
- Yeah, and we'll
steal that kid's toys.
He's got a lot of them.
- If we were good boys,
we'd get toys too.
- What's the fun in that?
It's no fun to be good.
Anyway, Santa Claus
doesn't care about us.
He's too far away.
- They're on to me.
Into the escape pod.
- Let's write him a
letter and tell him
we've been good as angels.
- Do you think he's
gonna fall for that?
- Sure, he will.
I'll be he can't even
see well anymore.
Too old to know what goes on.
- I have no idea what my
emotions are supposed to be.
- Me, too old?
Huh.
The Devil is very many
centuries older than I am.
- But the Devil works out.
- Those young kids
have got their nerve.
Next to the Devil,
I'm just a child.
It's just that I haven't
been well lately.
- Why, I haven't
had a good BM in...
- That really makes me...
let's see who those boys are.
- Heat up the death ray.
- We'll see what they're up to.
- Santa's gonna to get down.
- There you are,
you little rascals.
Well, you might as well
know I can see and hear
everything you say.
I know when you've
been bad or good.
- Did you hear that?
- I'll say.
Let's get out of here.
- Oh, damn, I had
the speaker on.
- My dear Santa Claus.
- Ooh, is this Van
Cliburn's apartment?
- Only thing that I wish for...
- I would love a
linen lampshade.
is for my parents can stay with
me tonight before Christmas.
I don't like...
- You.
to be alone.
- Oh.
- But the most
important thing...
- Is my fake writing.
bring me a little brother...
- Or people will die.
just about my age, because
I get awfully bored.
- Call me Ishmael.
I was born in a house
my father built.
The minute Yossarian...
- Please, Mr. Ruth,
hit a home run for me.
- I know it's hard for you, but
maybe you could get me a papa.
That would be super,
or just even a mama.
- A train with lots...
- My office instructed to
wire you up to $25,000.
Stop.
Hee-haw.
bicycle too.
- Why didn't he have his
secretary write this letter?
- Young Bill Gates
writing a letter.
- An airplane that will fly.
- And I want a ball.
- And could I have
my feet unbound?
good pair of shoes
to wear on Sunday.
- And as my two little brothers
have behaved very well...
- Write it.
Write it!
- You must see that
they get everything.
- Santa's such a sucker.
(Christmas music)
- It's big band Santa.
- Yabba do-ba, ba da-ba.
- I'm telling you, Pappy,
these Comedy Central contests
are a waste of time.
(Christmas music)
(Clock ticking)
(Explosion noise)
- Now I'm feeling disgruntled.
Grr.
- Santa Claus.
Santa Claus.
- Comma, Finland.
- Santa Claus.
Santa Claus.
- You guys ever hear
of this Santa Claus?
- Santa Claus.
Santa Claus.
- (singing) Crying.
- Santa Claus.
Santa Claus.
- May I just point
out that Toscanini
works at the post office.
- Oh, Santa has the
power to reverse film.
- Oh!
(Chuckling)
(Thump)
- Oh, there was a
rock in that one.
- Ho, ho, ho.
There's a dollar in every one.
My chain letter scam worked.
Ho, ho, ho.
- Marvelous.
Stupendous.
Just look at all those letters.
- Mailbox of values.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
- St. Nicholas.
Santa Claus.
- I still rule.
Eat my dust, Easter Bunny.
Oh, I'm more popular than Jesus.
- Oh, jeez, I need a database.
- Let's see here.
Dear Santa, I'm an elderly
woman who doesn't enjoy sex.
- My dear Santa Claus.
This year, I have
behaved very well.
I have been obedient.
- It's from a poodle.
- And have studied very much.
For that reason, please try
to bring me these toys...
a toy automobile, a submarine,
a football, a bat,
roller skates,
a scooter, a cannon, a rocket,
a bicycle, an atomic laboratory,
a machine gun.
- Oh, it's from Qaddafi.
- Whew.
Ooh.
Golly.
- Why, that's filthy.
No, I can't bring you that.
No.
- And many thanks.
Huh.
- Oy gevalt.
- So be it.
- (singing) I've written
a letter to Daddy.
- And as my two little brothers
have behaved very well... hmm.
- From Erik and Lyle Menendez.
- You must see to it
that they get everything.
Huh, a falsehood.
Hmm.
- See?
There's no fooling Santa Claus.
- Oh, yeah?
So who talked him
into that suit?
- Huh.
Into the liars box.
- Santa's really into labeling.
- Dear Santa Claus.
Please bring me
a little brother.
- Ho, ho, ho.
Ho, ho.
Can do.
- Here's one for you, Mr. Stork.
(Chuckling)
- I just sent him a coupon
for half off a little brother.
- I'm feeling good.
I think I'll go have
myself a Rumple Minze now.
- Meanwhile, in the sweatshop.
- Attention, everybody.
- Quiet, it's the old man.
He's announcing layoffs.
- The hour is drawing
near for me to go down
to Earth, where all good
children expect my arrival.
- Hey, listen up.
- Christmas Eve is almost here.
- What?
- But we still have thousands...
- Did he say, blessed
are the cheesemakers?
- Let's all make a big effort
to get our work finished.
- Whatever.
- It's up to you.
(Chuckling)
- Yeah, that's
great, but Santa's
pep talks don't pay the rent.
How about a little
pay hike, big man?
(Theme music)
(Laughter)
- Sorry about the
blindfold, Mike.
- Yeah, we just didn't
have enough wrapping paper
for your Christmas present.
- So, with the help of a French
communications satellite that
just happened to be in range
for a minutes, we give you...
- Take off your blindfold, Mike.
(Cymbals noise)
- The Family Nelson.
- Guys, this isn't...
isn't my family.
- Oh, look how happy they
are to see you, Mike.
- But this... this
isn't my family.
- Oh, Mike, I can just
imagine all the warm memories
you must have of
these, your loved ones.
- Tom, this isn't my family.
- But... but they're
the Nelsons, Mike.
- Well, they're a
Nelson, but there's
more than one
Nelson in the world.
- Oh, that explains
the 700 other Nelsons
in the Green Bay phone book.
- Yeah?
I'm not from Green Bay.
- Hey, sir, ma'am?
Uh, we're really
sorry about all this.
Uh, you see, there was some
sort of mix-up with
my buddies here.
- Oh, that'll happen.
- Yeah.
So, uh... well, you
know, we gotta get going.
Because, you know,
we're up in space.
And, you know, we
got... you know.
- Well, that's different.
- Yeah.
Well, uh... again,
we're... we're real sorry.
- Well, Dad?
- Yeah, I suppose.
- Yeah, OK.
Well, happy holidays.
And bye-bye.
You too there.
Bye-bye.
- Well, it's the thought
that counts, isn't it.
- Yeah.
Uh, your family anything
like those Nelsons, Mike?
- Oh, yeah, a little.
Uh, only they're
not so emotional.
(Chuckling)
(Buzzer sounding)
- Oh, no, we got movie sign.
Let's go!
- Here's a list of all the
gifts, names, and addresses.
- Well, just put it over there.
Well, thank heaven I still
have a very good memory, eh,
and I know every
single child on Earth.
- Isn't that right, Pueblo?
Uh, Paco.
Uh, or whatever.
- He's really going
downhill fast.
- Well, just to make sure, why
don't you take it with you?
- I've really got to hurry.
It's almost time for
the crystal clock
on the wall to strike 10:00.
- Don't forget that you've got
to return to the castle ahead
of the sunrise,
because the Sun will
turn the reindeer into dust.
- How many Christmases
you done, kid?
- I'll be here, all right.
In that case, I couldn't
get back to the castle.
And on what they use
for food, I'd perish.
Because here our
main food is pastries
and ice cream made
of soft clouds...
(gagging)
- What food do they eat
on Earth, Santa Claus?
- Oh, everything in sight.
They eat most of the animals,
the plants, the flowers,
the roots, birds, even
smoke and alcohol.
- And they eat at Hardee's.
- But enough of this talking.
We're wasting time,
and I must be off.
(Beeping)
- Nice van horn, Kringle.
- (singing) I'm not scared of
dying, and I don't really care.
- Everybody.
- (singing) Merry Christmas,
everybody, everybody.
Say goodbye to Santa Claus.
He is leaving...
- Hope they know
they're not going with.
- (singing) And a sack
of Christmas toys.
(Smashing sounds)
- Well, only 37
billion gifts to go.
- (singing) Hurry
up, my children.
Get on with your packing.
It's the night for Santa Claus
to fill all those stockings.
- Nice aria, Santa.
(Children singing)
- Thanks a lot, Rolf.
- (singing) Merry, merry
greetings I take to one
and all.
So hurry if you want to
enjoy the Yuletide fun.
- (singing) I'll see you in
your nightmares, a rum-pum,
pum-pum-pum.
(Smashing sounds)
- Hey, my Ovation.
- This will be mine one day.
- Bone in my hair?
I'm from Detroit.
- Now Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas to all.
- Merry Christmas.
- Every year we've got to
sing a fruity send-off song.
No wonder the elves quit.
- Let's see if I
have everything.
The bag with the powders for
dreaming of joy and goodwill.
Hey, it's Closey, the
closed caption kid.
- The golden key that...
- Cuckoo, cuckoo, cuckoo.
- The sleigh.
And now I'd better make sure
my reindeer are running.
- So I'm OD'd on
whimsy right now.
- Yes, Santa's sleigh is
really a huge toy sleigh.
- No!
- And he has to wind it like
any other toy to make it go.
- Oh, kind of technical here.
You wouldn't understand.
- It lives.
- Oh, Santa, you miracle worker.
- Ha.
Hey, Mike.
- Yeah?
- That deer is feeling
pretty cranky right now.
Ha!
Get it?
Cranky.
Ha.
Deer.
It... um.
- No.
This isn't charming at all.
It's creepy.
- Help us.
(Laughing)
- Well, when Santa laughs, the
whole world shakes its head.
(Laughter)
(laughing)
- My god, what's happening?
- Huh.
- Yeah?
- Uh, a pentagram and
reindeer laughing.
You figure it out.
(Christmas music)
- Be off, my reindeer, and
glide through the heavens
as fast as you can go.
May my palace of gold
and crystal enjoy peace.
And Jesus, the Son of
God, join us on Earth
so that we can all
have joy and goodwill.
- This is weird theology.
- Wait, open the garage door!
Oh, that's...
(crashing noise)
- Well, Santa, I guess
all us three-year-olds
will just fend for ourselves.
Don't worry about us.
- So Mike, is this St. Cloud?
(Chuckling)
- That's two.
- Because it's clouds.
- Oh darn, forgot my Chapstick.
Whatever.
I'm telling you,
Blixen, he's gained
about 30 pounds since last year.
I don't think I can hold out.
(Panting)
- Uh, this is Houston, Santa.
We're tracking you on radar.
Seem to be having some trouble
there with the primary thrust
system.
Uh, repeat, eject now.
- Uh-oh.
Santa got drunk and delivered
all the gifts to the moon
again.
- Whew, that was close.
- Well, no.
- He almost ran into the moon.
- Just take my word for it.
- And here's the planet Earth.
- Well, kind of.
- I wonder where
Santa will go first.
Europe?
Africa?
America?
- Ripple pines?
(singing) I like
to live in America.
Cadillacs zoom in America.
- Think of all the nice things
you'll get from Santa Claus.
- Yes, Mama.
- That's a good boy.
- Or a girl.
- See you in the morning.
- If you get bored,
you can go down
and practice your piano lesson.
See you later, my darling.
- Our love's implied.
Goodbye.
Maybe we can do
this again sometime.
You seem like a nice kid.
- Ugh.
Why do they leave me
so heavily medicated?
Um, were... were my
parents just here?
If I could just get some
movement in my legs.
(Whimpering)
- I knew it.
The Devil is nearby,
and these three
certainly are up to no good.
- OK, listen now.
As soon as Santa Claus lands
on the roof here,
all three of us
will jump on him.
We'll tie him up and
we'll stick him in a sack.
And then we'll go home
with all of Santa's toys.
- But what about Santa?
- We can make him our slave,
and all of the candies and toys
will belong to us.
- Gee, nice kids.
- So whenever we
want something...
- Oh boy, this is gonna be fun.
- Better not talk now.
He can hear, so get away.
- Isn't kidnapping
Santa a federal offense?
- I think so.
- No, a strolling Gallagher.
- Ugh.
(Music playing)
- It's a Fellini Christmas.
- Attica!
Attica!
- Time for bed.
Santa Claus will be
here any minute now.
- Mama, and who is Santa Claus?
- He's the man in the store,
the one with the red suit
and the white beard that
was laughing very much.
- And does Santa know about me?
- Uh-huh.
- Is he real, like my daddy?
- No, not really.
- Would you shut the
bloody organ grinder up?
- Probably French.
- Hey.
- And comes here once a year.
- Who does he come for?
- They say he gives those to
children who are obedient.
- I don't think he likes me.
He has never brought
me any dollies.
- It's...
- He's just jealous.
not that.
Maybe you're forgetting
to ask him for dollies.
- Yeah, bull!
- And if I ask him for one now?
- Go ahead.
- Make my day.
- Perhaps he'll hear you.
We can say a prayer, dear.
- Mama, please don't cry.
- You will stain my dress.
- It's just that it's Christmas.
And Christmas always
makes me feel sad.
- You and a lot of other people.
- Mommy, what is
Christmas good for.
- Well, to remind us that
Christ was born many years ago.
- Craig?
- I don't think so.
- And he was even
poorer than we are.
- Whoa.
- He was born in a bed of straw.
- Know what, Mama?
- I don't buy it.
- I already asked Santa
Claus for two pretty dollies.
If he brings me two, I'll
give one to little Jesus.
- Oh, he's got plenty
of presents already.
- Yes, my darling.
Maye if we pray with
all of our might, hmm?
- Oh, look at that.
The roof's leaking.
I thought I spackled that.
(Christmas music)
- (singing) Shotgun
shells, BB's in the air.
If I don't find a break
in this cloud cover,
I'm never gonna make it.
(Music playing)
- Plink, plink, plink, plink.
Pizzicato plink, plink.
Come legato in.
- Knick-knack, paddywhack,
give a dog a bone.
- While Santa steers his
sleigh towards Earth...
- Disaster awaits.
- Old devil Pitch
awaits his arrival.
Here comes Santa now.
First stop, Mexico City.
- Manure dust
overtakes the sleigh.
- Oh, Santa, I need
some stuff, man.
Just a taste.
Come on, man.
- It's freezing.
I wish I were back in
Hades, tending the furnaces.
(Santa laughing)
- He's heard Santa.
- Well, I hope so,
with ears like that.
- Boy, he's really hauling ass.
- And it's his.
- By Satan, there he is.
I'm committed and
I'm prepared to upset
his own merry Christmas.
Heh, heh.
- I love my work.
- We will see who wins out.
This is one night that
no one can take from me.
- He has kind of
an oily complexion.
- What's he going to do?
- You tell us.
- Oh-ho.
He's going to push
the chimney out
of place so that
poor old Santa won't
be able to enter this house.
- Well, that nut.
(Chuckling)
- I love Ron Reagan Jr.
- Hmm.
Satan, honey, no.
Ooh.
- Don't ever do that again.
(Vomiting noise)
- (singing) The
Devil is a wiener.
Wiener, wiener, wiener.
- Well, I'll park in
the ramp this time.
- Don't do that with your hands.
Don't.
(Christmas music)
- Oof.
(Helicopter sounds)
- So this is all the
toys in the world
for all the children
in the world?
- Yep.
- Hefty, hefty, hefty.
- Wimpy, wimpy, wimpy.
- Oh, come on.
This is a very difficult
move for this actor.
- You know what, Santa?
It's about 4:00 AM.
You'd better get a rush on.
- Ugh.
Ugh.
- Terpsichore.
- Whew, that was
some action sequence.
Whew.
- He's got a Stephen King
manuscript in that bag.
- Let's hope Santa
realizes what's happened.
(Grunting)
- Oops.
- Well, what's happened here?
I can smell sulfur.
- Oh, sorry, that was me.
- Well, that must explain this.
That old devil Pitch
must be around here.
(Grunting)
- Jim J. Bullock is more
frightening than that devil.
- Hi, Mr. Rush.
- Santa's determined to get in.
He'll find a way.
He's not one to give up.
- O-ho, got some
plastique in here.
Fragmentation bomb.
- Well, time for a Mai Tai.
Big one, too.
- Well, there's more than
one way to beat the Devil.
Santa will jump down
using his magic parasol.
- With a 10-point
degree of difficulty.
- Old Pitch hadn't
counted on this.
- Doh!
- He's almost green with anger.
- And it took a fly gang
of 16 to lower Santa down.
- Tuck and roll,
Kringle, tuck and roll.
- I'm frustrated.
- He's good.
(Alarm sounds)
- It is the witching
hour, my friend.
- Uh-oh.
These two seem to know that
Santa's in the living room.
Look out, Santa,
they'll see you.
(Sound of shotgun
racking and firing)
- Yeah.
Well, that's the last
thing they'll ever see.
- Why, of course.
Santa can handle this.
All he has to do is
use the magic dreaming
powders prepared by Mr. Merlin.
- And Mr. Owsley.
- And it isn't long before
our two little stay-up-lates
are sleeping soundly
in their bed.
- Unfortunately, the powder
does have contraindications
and enduring side effects.
(Music playing)
- (singing) It's
the Devil's theme.
He's doing a little song.
Even though he's the
embodiment of evil,
he's still got a goofy song.
In his tights he brings
death, despair, disruption,
and disease.
Now let's all join him,
and I'll laugh along.
Devil.
- Now what?
Must be Pitch putting the
chimney back in place.
- Son of a... this time I'm
putting my patent leather shoe
down... permanently.
- Ha.
This year I gave
everyone Yahtzee.
(Vomiting sound)
- Ha, ha.
- Hey, pitch black.
Ha.
Because of the...
- It's a living.
Huh.
(Chuckling)
(Maniacal laughter)
- Oh, gotcha.
- Well, the Devil
doesn't give up either.
And he seems to be quite
happy about his next plot
against Santa.
- No.
No.
He enjoys pantaloons
more than he should.
- Hey!
- Santa is filmed on location
with the men and women
of Broward County, Florida.
- Ok.
OK, if I join your ranks, will
you stop dancing like that?
- Could Santa be coming
down this chimney now?
- Yes.
- Uh-oh.
He's all right,
but that was close.
- Santa, stop, drop, and roll.
- Red Adair is brought in
to extinguish the fire.
- Watch out for the backdraft.
(Cackling)
- Am I alone in here?
Hello?
- But suddenly he thinks
of something else to do.
- More impish pranks?
Ho, ho!
- Bah, he, ho, hum.
- That's it.
He'll huff and puff until
his burning breath turns
the doorknob and keyhole red-hot
so that the magic key won't
work and Santa will
burn his hands.
- What is this, "Home
Alone 3, the Quickening"?
- Metal conducts heat very
well, and Satan knows that.
- First, he'll see
if it's hot enough.
- Then he'll add the clam sauce.
- What do you think of that?
- Not much.
- But Santa sees
what Pitch is up to.
And he isn't afraid.
- I'm afraid.
- Oh, I saw his ribs.
Ick.
- This place is a piece of cake.
- Fa, la, la, la, la, la, la.
(Humming)
- Fa, la, la.
- (singing) Oh, the bells.
Oh, the jolly, jolly bells.
- Meanwhile, Pitch
looks out the window
to watch Santa burn
his hands He doesn't
seem to know he's
right behind him.
- Ha!
- It's like having Dom
DeLuise sneaking up on you.
- Ha, ha.
Let's see, a little more
Tide and the napalm's ready.
Heh, heh.
- O-ho, a cannon.
Now it's Santa's turn
to get even with Pitch.
- Now, isn't this bringing
Santa down to Satan's level?
Mean.
- Santa's a lifetime
member of the NRA.
- Hey!
Ouch!
Ow!
- This is funny.
I don't care what anybody says.
- Ow.
Ow.
Ouch.
Ooh.
(Laughter)
- I enjoy inflicting pain.
I should call the elves.
They'd love this.
- Oh, brother.
(Theme music)
- Santa burns like a tire fire.
- Uh, is this the
recycling center?
- This is the Johnson house.
It's the second time
I've hit them today.
(Straining)
- Ugh.
Oof.
Just sneak in here,
and they'll never, uh,
have any idea that
I was ever... waah!
- Kid, you're a great audience.
Mwah.
(Christmas music)
- (singing) It is to ride
in Santa's underwear.
- (sobbing) I love Christmas.
- Well, let's see.
Over-sized tomato.
Stock options from
the Sharper Image.
Lug nuts.
Cable ACE award.
Oh, that's no good.
Spark plug gapper.
Hmm.
- Like it?
- Don't you wrap any
of this stuff, Santa?
- Oof!
Ho, ho.
There we go.
Merry Chri... oh, shh.
- Hey, kid, where's the pantry?
- I know all those toys
don't make you happy.
- So I'm taking them back.
- But I'll do something
for you that I only
do for children
who are very good.
- I'll sing "Proud Mary."
- I'll let you see me as I am.
And therefore, I
will use the powders
that will make you
dream that you're awake.
- Now, this gets weird,
so I'll warn you.
You may want to leave the room.
- And you're not allergic
to anything, are you?
- And now...
- A word from our sponsor.
- Awaken while you're dreaming.
- Summer of my
German stormtrooper.
- He's a young Barton Fink.
- Uh.
Uh.
Hermann Goering?
Uh, oh no, Santa.
- Out, vile jelly.
(Jazz trumpet sounds)
- Like what you see, kid?
- I want to be a dentist.
- Hey, hey, I just shined those.
- You love me, don't you?
Say you you love me, Santa.
- (singing) La, la, la, la.
La, la, la, la.
- Of course I love you, sonny,
just as much as your parents.
- Well?
- Because no one loves a
child as much as his parents.
Only at times the parents don't
understand their children,
and the children don't
understand their parents.
- Huh.
- And are you really
sure that they
love me when I'm left all alone?
- Yes, of course they love you.
And you must believe
they love you.
And now...
- A word from our sponsors.
- Go back to sleep again.
- Phew.
I think he bought it.
Hey, quit drooling on my beard.
- It was all a sweet dream.
- Now, you just practice
your piano if you need love.
- When you awaken...
- You'll be Rick Wakeman.
- I wish you much happiness.
- And oh say, can I use
the can before I go?
(Beeping)
- All right, hold it, Kringle.
We've got the place surrounded.
Come out with your bag up.
Your reindeer have
turned themselves in.
(Floorboards squeaking)
- Oops.
No. There.
No.
Oh, there we go.
All right, there.
Ahem.
- (singing) That
cuckoo Tannenbaum.
- A pleasure to
say hello to you.
- Hi.
Did you leave that brat at home?
- Oh, you bet.
He's such a pain.
- I know.
- Merry Christmas.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye, dear.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
- Putz.
Never liked that guy.
- It's been a long time
since I've seen the Martins.
- Flaming Moe's!
- They're both looking pretty
well, though, aren't they?
- Uh, the steaming red fellow
at the bar sent these over.
- Oh.
- That's a strange
cocktail, isn't it?
- It's the Cocktail
of Remembrance
which only I can prepare.
Whoever drinks it will think
of that which is most dear,
and which at times for
some unknown reason
we seem to forget.
- Did I say, "I'm Pat and
I'll be your waiter" yet?
- Perhaps we need a reminder.
Very possibly we've
forgotten someone we love.
- Barney.
- Love can be
expressed in many ways.
But the truest
love is that which
we give without expecting
anything in return.
- Waiter.
Wai... waiter!
- Hey, can I get some
service over here?
Check, please.
- We really need to order.
We gotta hit a movie.
- You will become
aware of that love
which is closest to your heart.
- Oh, and keep the glass.
- They couldn't
drink this cocktail,
as it would burn their throats.
- Uh, let's just get
a bottle of wine.
- Well, since we are
very much in love...
- Why don't you bring us
the Nachos Magnificos?
- May it always be that way.
- (singing) Strange brew.
(Guitar sound)
- Uh, why is our waiter
stripping, honey?
- Now, that's strange.
- My pants tickle.
- Where'd he disappear to?
- I don't think he
was just a waiter.
- He's the night manager too.
- He didn't seem
to be a stranger.
That kind look.
The white beard.
- The spike heels.
- I knew that face
when I was a child.
- Couldn't be.
- If his beard was white
when you were a small girl,
he'd be dead and buried by now.
- Oh, you always know
the right thing to say.
- Now, that's strange.
- I'm Adolph Margaux.
- I suddenly have an urge
to see our little boy.
- Little boy?
Oh.
- Poor Billy's always alone.
I feel that he's needing us too.
- Ha!
- He'll be so glad.
- Come on.
- Booze helps parents
care for their children.
- Hey, I got a dine and
dash on table seven.
- Honey, do you smell gas?
- Well, he's not playing the
piano, so he's not bored.
- Uh, you probably don't
remember us, sonny.
I... I'm your mother,
and this is your father.
- And I love what they've
done with the room.
- Well, we're off.
- Well, three houses
down, 650 billion to go.
Ho, ho, ho.
- Pitch hasn't done too well
by himself against Santa,
so he's back to seek the help
of these boys who so far are
the only ones willing to
listen to his evil plans.
They may think it's
smart to help him now,
but they'll be sorry,
for his advice can only
get them into trouble.
- Invest in junk bonds.
- Better get over there
behind the water tank
and take the rope along.
When we spot Santa Claus,
zowie, we'll pull the rope
and knock him down.
- Got it.
That's for me.
- So Satan can only get three
little boys to follow him?
- Well, it's probably
a pyramid scheme,
so these kids get in
on the ground floor.
- I see.
- Hey, Willy, cover me!
(Machine gun sounds)
- Uh, the thing of it is, Bob, I
got a bad feeling on this one.
I don't think I'm
gonna make it out.
- See, it works.
- Didn't I tell you?
- Oh, boy.
- Attaboy.
Santa's on his way.
- Get your head down.
Here comes Santa.
- Santa was close now.
I could feel it.
- Waiting is the worst part.
- I can't hear you.
Ha, ha.
(Suspenseful music)
- Tell me you
heard that bassoon.
- Incoming!
Hit the hole!
Incoming!
- I'm hit, man, I'm hit.
I'm hit!
- How can you be so dumb?
Stupid fools.
You certainly turned our
plan into a horrible mess.
- Maybe you could
support us, Stan.
- I can promise you that.
I'll make him pay
dearly for all this.
Ooh!
- You know, I'm
not going to re-up.
- That scared me.
The light almost blinded me.
That music was so loud.
- It scared me too.
What a noise.
- Whitesnake was awesome.
- Maybe Santa Claus left
something in our house.
Shall we go see?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
(Suspenseful music)
- Fritz Reiner leads
the Chicago Symphony
in the sparkling dance of Pitch.
It's fantastic.
- Some present
for our Christmas.
- Santa Claus doesn't like us.
- We didn't get anything.
- Jeez, I gotta spoon
feed you little brats.
(Whispering)
- Satan, could you
speak up, please?
- It's all your fault.
It was your idea.
- Don't be a sissy.
We're not complaining.
Well, anyway, it
was his idea that we
should go up on the roof.
- My idea?
- The movement is
disintegrating.
- I'm going to bed.
I'm tired.
- Coward!
You kicked me when
my back was turned.
- This is almost too easy.
- He's a liar.
It wasn't me.
- In that case, it was you.
And you haven't got the
nerve to say you did it.
- Nope.
- My hinder.
- That's it.
That's it.
Terrific.
Ha, ha, ha.
Ah, beat your brains out.
At least I've got them battling.
Lucifer will be very pleased.
- I really think I have a
shot at the ham this year.
- I'll beat you.
- Let me go.
- Ouch!
Ouch.
- Hey, cut it out.
- See you later.
- Hi, folks.
Welcome back to the Satellite.
As a special treat,
Crow, Tom, and I
have written and are going to
perform an original Christmas
carol.
- Uh.
Uh, Mike, it's not
just for Christmas.
It's for holidays of all faiths.
- Yeah, and don't,
uh, call it a carol
because Carol is a
woman's name and we
want this song to
be all-inclusive.
- Right.
Why don't you hit it, Cambot?
There we go.
(Music playing)
- (singing) Let us all now sing
our praises to the Lord today.
Although you may not
share our belief system,
which is perfectly OK.
- (singing) Maybe you
worship an abstract being.
That is kind of vague.
Or maybe you just worship
a guy whose name is Greg.
- (singing) Perhaps your
religion doesn't include,
uh, the time called Lent.
But whatever your religion,
we support you 100%.
- (singing) So sit
around the fire.
And have a chestnut roast.
- Chestnut.
- (singing) Or raise
a glass in toast.
- A glass in toast.
- (singing) To "Happy
Days'" Donny Most.
- (singing) But if you prefer to
eat Indian food on Christmas
Day.
I can only shrug my
shoulders and say, Namaste.
Namaste.
- (singing) Personally I prefer
turkey, gravy, and salad.
But let's never forget
all cultures are valid.
- (singing) So let's have
peace on Earth and cut out all
the bull.
Let's have a holiday season
that's multicultural.
- (singing) If there's one
point we'd like to make
with this festive holiday song.
- (singing) It's that Christmas
comes just once a year,
so for a few days,
for crying out loud,
can we all just get along?
- Wow.
- That was actually pretty good.
- That was great.
- It was lovely.
- Hey, good job.
- Very nice.
- Thank you.
(Theme music)
- Ooh.
- I'm filled with mirth.
- Oh, no.
Mr. Pitch has decided
to steal Santa's sleigh.
- Good thing Santa
uses The Club.
- That's a relief.
The reindeer won't obey him.
Tough luck, Pitch.
- Yeah, wind-up reindeer are
fiercely loyal to their masters
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh-oh, a pair of scissors.
- Don't run with them now.
- Look out, Santa!
- Ugh.
Jeez, I shouldn't eat
everything they set out for me.
You'd think after 1,600
years, I'd know that by now.
I'd better hit the Easy Glide.
Ugh.
Oh, boy.
Gotta get the suspension
checked on this sled anyway.
It's starting to
list to this side.
Ugh.
Oh, boy.
- Santa should, uh, check
that exhaust system.
(Coughing)
- Cat.
- Aw, nothing in the
lobster trap today.
- Santa's mounting up procedures
don't make for good cinema.
- Yeah, it's like
watching Hoss mount up.
- And get on his horse.
- Smell sulfur.
That old devil Pitch
must be around somewhere.
- Oh, my.
Mr. Merlin's magic
dreaming powders.
- Un-cut.
- Now Santa won't be able
to put anyone to sleep.
- Except now.
- On, my heavenly reindeer,
for there's much to be done.
(Coughing)
- Doh.
Red man.
Ooh.
- And there goes the
Flower to Disappear.
And now Santa won't be able
to make himself invisible.
What are you going
to do now, Santa?
- I'm going to Disney World.
- All references to Disney
World are the property
of the Walt Disney Corporation.
- I feel the need,
the need for speed.
- Suddenly, Santa corkscrews
into Ypsilanti, Michigan.
(Sound of aircraft diving)
- You can much sense the
string there, can't you?
- Yeah.
- Let us hope the
Flower to Disappear
doesn't fall into bad hands.
- Like Jose Canseco's?
- We get him?
Huh?
- The new Vertical Takeoff
and Landing Santa Claus.
- On wings.
- Santa's got a brand new bag.
(Humming)
- Oh, this doesn't look like...
oh, right, just gotta stop
and ask for directions.
- Oh, darn, this is the
Finkelstein's house.
- Huh?
- Uh, fortunately, uh,
Santa took arc welding
at, uh, junior college.
- And refrigeration.
- Meanwhile, Santa
goes on his way,
not knowing that his dreaming
powders and Flower to Disappear
are gone.
- Santa lives in
a world of denial.
(Jolly laughter)
- Ha.
Ugh.
Um, anyway.
(Laughter)
- I'm just glad
it's not Marmaduke.
- Oh, crap.
- Santa is not
afraid of that dog.
- Is that right?
- If he goes after him, he
still thinks he can disappear.
- Oh, you don't say.
- Go get him, Dante.
Seek that old goat.
- Moms Mabley.
- Finish him off.
- How can old Pitch
be so mean, siccing
a vicious dog on
Santa like that?
- Well, that is his job.
- The powders.
The Flowers of Disappear.
- Oh, poopie.
- No powders?
And no Flower?
What do I do now?
- Run, Santa.
Climb the tree.
It's your only chance.
- This is definitely a major
embarrassment for Santa
and a significant
setback for his campaign.
(Barking)
(Laughter)
- Get down.
Go away.
Scotch.
Shoo.
Get out.
Ugh.
(Whimpering)
- That certainly was
a very funny sight,
old white beard and
his sack running
as if the Devil himself were
going to take him below.
- You'll pay for your mischief.
- I've got friends, Satan.
- Hmm.
But first you'll have to
come down from that tree.
And I can have a lot
of fun before you
can get rid of Dante.
Because you know
what I'm going to do?
I'm going to wake up everybody.
- Faugh!
Nobody can hear your voice.
- They hear it in the form of
their own private imagination
or ideas.
- Oh, now you're
just making it up.
- Let them see how
foolish you appear.
(Laughter)
- Toodles.
- It's Rob and Laura.
- There's a prowler out there.
- I want a glass of water.
- He's come to kill your
wife and your children.
He's really quite vicious.
- Give me some covers.
- He's hiding up in your tree.
Defend yourself.
He's going to murder you.
- I can't stress that enough.
(Whispering)
- Is it something you can
share with the whole class, Mr.
Lucifer?
- Mr. Merlin!
- Aw.
- Oh, no.
- Ooh.
(Shouting)
(Tarzan yodel)
- Apparently, no one is in
Santa's magic observatory.
- They're over at
the Keebler's place.
- Time to awaken.
There's a man outside.
- His name is Tim.
He asked if I could marry him.
Hee, hee!
- Marie?
Marie, get up.
I think that we're in danger.
- What?
- Yes.
- Oh, Rob.
- Assassin?
I'm not going.
- Hurry, get out of bed.
Go after him.
- Surely.
Where's the pistol?
- Where you keep it.
- In the drawer?
- In the drawer.
- Where in the drawer?
In this drawer?
- The National Rifle
Association presents
this playlet for your enjoyment.
- There it is.
Go after him.
- Come on, don't be funny.
- Me?
- Yes.
- But I... But I...
- El Don Knottso.
(Coughing)
- With this cough, I can't
be expected to go out.
I might catch pneumonia.
(Coughing)
- Ha.
- Ah!
- Come on.
Now get up.
Pneumonia or no
pneumonia, you go.
- But Marie, understand.
Why don't you go
and get your father?
- Get my father?
- Please.
- Wait a minute.
I must put on my robe.
- At home with Carl Rowan.
- Don't waste time.
- Rose Marie!
- Hi.
Can I use your phone
to call my machine?
Thank you.
- I'm, uh, ordering a Hawaiian
pizza, because I'm Satan.
Heh, heh.
- Help, police.
Help, police.
In the tree there's an assassin.
- This guy's really an
effective facilitator.
I'd like him on my staff.
- Grandfather!
- In with the bad air,
out with the good.
- (singing) Does
the Devil lose its
flavor on the bedpost overnight?
(Humming)
- Oh, he's made out of pumice.
- Ooh.
- There, done and done.
(Cackling)
- Hello?
I'm looking for Amanda Hugg.
- Fire Department.
Firemen.
Firemen!
The house is burning.
I'm on fire.
- The turtle called Gamera
is about to attack the city.
- (singing) Devil with the dance
belt, dance belt, dance belt,
devil with the dance belt on.
- It's Juan, the
Maytag repairman-o.
- This is a five-alarm fire.
Better let me have that
address, please, won't you?
- Don't expect anything
from Santa Claus.
He doesn't bring toys
to poor children.
- What a jerk.
- Didn't I tell you
to keep that doll?
Silly.
So now you won't have anything.
You are poor.
- Mama, Mama.
- We must rise up
against the bourgeoisie.
- Don't the poor people get
anything from Santa Claus?
- No.
Now let it rest.
- No, my darling.
Santa Claus is good to all of
the children who are obedient.
- But Santa oppresses
the proletariat.
poor or wealthy.
To bed now, my darling.
(Theme music)
- Your reindeer will
turn into powder.
You will starve to death.
And I will rule the Earth.
(Laughter)
- I don't get it.
(Sirens)
(Singing in french)
- I'm in control now,
right after wee-wees.
(Humming "william
tell overture")
- Ever since Walter Brennan
went camp, it's
been all downhill.
- Know how this run
this thing, old man.
Come on, get out of my way.
- Santa Claus?
Santa Claus?
It's me, Merlin.
- Merlin.
- Send me a pick me up bouquet.
Where are you?
- Here, in the observatory.
- Get out of there?
- What... what is the matter?
In Just a few minutes,
it's going to be day.
Return now.
- They've got me
in a tree, Merlin.
I dropped the
Flowers of Disappear.
- Oh, good one, Santa.
- And also the
powders for dreaming.
And this beast just
won't let me come down.
- Any feedback on that?
- All this confusion has
been prepared by Mr. Pitch.
- Wait now.
- Hurry, Mr. Merlin.
Hurry.
- Why doesn't Santa
give him another leg?
(Muttering)
- Doh, I forgot a quarter.
I'll just play some pinball
while I'm waiting here.
- Where can we find Santa Claus?
- I don't know.
That's why I got
you, Mr. Wizard.
- He's already been to
Asia, Europe, and Australia.
He must be on the
American continent.
- He's rollerblading
on Venice Beach.
- I think I see him.
He's in Mexico.
Oh, golly.
But he's in a terrible fix.
And there's no time
to go to his rescue.
- I'm old, you see.
- And the Sun is about to rise.
Bad dog.
Mad dog.
- Too much Mad Dog.
That's what did it.
- Against good is bad.
Against black is white.
Against a bad itch, scratch it.
Against thirst, water.
Against mad dog...
- Snap it up, Leon Russell.
- Against mad dog...
against mad dog...
- Never mind, it's too late.
The dog got him.
- A cat.
A cat.
- This guy trained
the king of England?
- A cat, Santa Claus, a cat.
- Please be quick, Merlin.
Now hear this.
My time is almost over.
This time it's serious.
- Against mad dog, a cat.
Use one of the toy
cats that you wind up.
- Santa's tenacious
jolliness is tested
when he's treed by a coon hound.
- I didn't know Santa
and Merlin were buddies.
- It's a mad, mad,
mad, mad, mad,
mad, mad, mad, mad, mad, mad,
mad, mad, mad, mad,
mad, mad, mad world.
- So he's gonna try
and breed the dog?
- Don't make me laugh, Santa.
- Shoo.
(Laughter)
- Ha, ha, it's a Hot Wheels cat.
Let's submit this
to "Doggone Funny."
- That's a tough driveway
to negotiate there.
- Let's go now.
All together now.
Don't push me.
Just a minute.
You make me nervous.
- Oh, come on, hurry up.
- I can handle this.
But don't leave me alone, huh?
- All right.
We're with you.
Come on.
- (singing) Indiana wants me.
Lord, I can't go back there.
- Where's the body?
How many are injured?
(Gasp)
- Hosni Mubarak.
- They'll surely find Santa.
- Nothing in sigh.
- We surely can't find Santa.
- Can't see anything.
Better look around.
- Don't push me.
Leave me alone.
Don't do that.
Hello.
Well, why don't you shoot?
- It's the last
episode of "AKA Pablo."
- Be careful. It
may be a whole gang.
But don't worry.
Try to be brave.
Be calm.
We must all be brave.
That's it, the hole.
(Shrieking)
- Montgomery, Alabama, 1955.
- We're wet!
- Hurry.
You barely have time now.
- I still have one
more friend to visit.
I mustn't fail her.
- But...
- No "buts" about it.
First come the children.
I'll see you later, if possible.
- Well, he was here, all right.
This is definitely Santa scat.
- What happened?
Did you find anyone?
- We've looked all
over the place.
- Wow, I'm insane, huh?
- Let's make sure
the fire's out.
- It's out.
- There's some smoke over there.
- Well, that serves him
right, the old troublemaker.
He'll probably catch pneumonia.
But he asked for it.
- Isn't he immortal?
What does he care
about pneumonia?
- Wait.
The Flower to Disappear
has fallen right
into Lupita's house.
- Just take my word on this.
It really happened.
- Yeah, I wanted to
be a figure skater.
I could have beat Peggy Fleming.
Could have been on
the "Sullivan Show."
Yeah, I could have had
Senor Wences' hand.
Uh, in marriage, I mean.
Yeah, I could have
been somebody.
Oh, no.
(Mumbling)
- Diarrhea is like a storm
raging outside your home.
- I think the Wallendas
are sneaking in.
- Well, bring me up, Walt.
(Snapping sound)
- Oops.
- Raus!
(Screaming in german)
- Hi, I'm Santa for
Citizens Against Gillnets.
Oh.
- Did you find work?
- Nothing, my dear.
Nothing.
- I stayed at the bar
all night Christmas Eve,
and not even one job offer.
- Well, shall we open the gift?
Oh, never mind.
Well, I could carve the
turk... oops, forget it.
Never mind.
- Hmm.
- Are we still poor?
- Mama.
I saw Santa Claus.
I'm very happy again.
He couldn't stay and talk to
me for a very long time...
- Right here on our stage,
ladies and gentlemen.
because his white reindeer
would turn into powder.
- You must have had
Mexican food for dinner.
- But now go back to sleep.
It is very late.
Just go ahead and think of
all those wonderful things.
- Then was I just
dreaming, Mama?
Didn't Daddy leave me a
dolly outside in the patio?
- What?
You accusing me of
not looking for a job?
- Not this one.
- But he said it was
a beautiful dolly.
- Allow me to illustrate
my point for you.
Excuse me.
"New York Times"?
When did we start getting "New
York Times" home delivery?
- Wow.
- Hey, that's not a
doll, that's a sister.
Whoa.
- Look it, Mommy.
It's indeed a pretty dolly?
- Put the doll down, honey.
Just back away from
it very slowly.
- Well, it's kind of an
empty miracle with very
short-lived consequences, but...
- In the name of Santa,
Merlin, and the elves.
Amen.
- Don't cry for me, Argentina.
- Could I play with
your dolly too?
- Hey, I could use
a little help here.
- Great, another mouth to feed.
- Know what, Mama?
Let's start a train out there...
- Let's start a
Chinese restaurant?
and candy.
- Ok.
- The home of Santa Claus.
He's just arriving with his
sleigh and white reindeer.
- It's a Rue McClanahan doll.
- Thank you, Santa Claus.
Goodbye, Santa Claus.
Thank you for a wonderful
and amazing Christmas.
- Oh no, a Scud.
It's going to nail Santa.
- And so once again, Santa
returns to his palace
from his yearly
Christmas rounds.
He is happy, gay.
- Oh.
- For once again
he has brought joy
to the children of the world.
- Ho, ho.
Oh, I forgot France.
Oh, well.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
- Why don't they look?
Oh.
- Blessed are they who believe,
for they shall see God.
- I didn't know
it was that easy.
- Peace on Earth.
Good will toward men.
- And women.
- Merry Christmas.
- Hey, it doesn't
say Merry Christmas.
Oh.
- Yeah, I suppose it does.
- Next week, Jesus and
the Oak Ridge Boys.
- Happy Holidays from
American Family Insurance.
(Music playing)
- (singing) I'll be
home for Christmas.
You can't...
- Hi.
What's the matter, honey.
You look a little
geshmudlikeit or something.
I don't know.
- I don't know.
I guess, here I am on
the Satellite, and...
- Oh, you'll snap
out of it, Mike.
So, what's the deal?
Any more presents in here, huh?
- No, no.
Come on, Mike, open up.
I'll bet you miss Earth.
Something about the
time of year, maybe?
- Well, I'll tell
you what I miss.
You know, I miss the
change of seasons.
You know, up here
on the Satellite
it's just 365 days
of nice weather.
And that's OK, but
I miss the crisp air
and, you know, I miss putting
on a sweater and going outside.
And you know what
I miss most of all?
I... I miss the pure
beauty of the snowfall
as it piles up as
Christmas draws nigh.
- Ah.
- Hey, you guys!
You guys, look!
Look! Look!
- Whoa!
- Wow!
- Cambot, give me
rocket number nine.
- Wow.
- [All] Ooh.
- [Cambot] It's a
Christmas miracle.
- Yeah, looks like
a wet miracle.
And I'm not shoveling it.
- Oh.
- Good gravy, people.
Don't you realize
what this means?
We have a snow day!
- Woo-hoo!
- That's right, a snow day!
A snow day!
Uh, is that good?
- Is it good? that's the best.
- Yeah.
- Hey mad fools, we're not
going to be around a while.
Uh, I'm going to put
on my space suit.
We're all going
outside, and we're
going to build a snow fort.
- Yay!
Let's go.
- Snow fight.
- Woo-hoo!
- Ah.
- Uh, Mr. Pitch?
- Pitch.
- Oh, Pitch.
Uh, I assume you know I
truly, truly admire your work.
- Great, thanks.
- More pie, man ghost?
- Oh, no, I shouldn't.
It's good, though.
- Frank, he likes your pie.
- Yo, Pitch.
Pitch.
The things you've done,
the things you've seen.
You are eternal, aren't you?
- I tell you, I can
feel it some days too.
(Laughter)
- He can feel it, he says.
Heh, heh.
- So, what's on the
agenda for old Pitch?
- Well, I'm laying low
until after the holidays.
Starting next week, though, I
engulf the world in darkness.
- Ooh.
- [Santa] Ho, ho, ho, ho.
That's what you think, buster.
Ha.
I'm here to eat candy
canes and kick ass,
and I'm all out of candy canes.
Ha, ha, come on.
- Oh, Frank, think of it.
A full-tilt battle between
pure evil and Santa Claus
in our own home.
- This is the best
Christmas ever.
- Happy holidays, everyone.
- Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Ugh!
(Christmas music)
(Maniacal laughter)